valuedopinions.co.in 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy: Valued Opinions

The Valued Opinions websites are owned and operated by Research Now Limited, a UK company, ("Research Now"). Research Now Group, Inc. (formerly known as e-Rewards, Inc.)  (a US company), e-Rewards Europe Limited (a UK company), Research Now, Inc. (a US company), Research Now Limited (a UK company), The Mobile Panel Ltd., The Mobile Channel Ltd., Research Now Pty Ltd. (an Australian company), Research Now Inc. (a Canadian company), Research Now Consulting Co. Ltd (a Chinese company), Research Now Technology EPE (a Greek company), Research Now GmbH (a German company), Research Now PTE LTD (a Singaporian company), Research Now Pty Limited (a New Zealand company), Research Now Spain S.L. (a Spanish company) and Research Now SARL (a French company) together form the Research Now group. This Privacy Policy governs the website located at www.valuedopinions.in.

Below we have set out how we use the information that you give us and how the Site operates.

 **Subject Information Statement**

Research Now processes your personal data (as defined by the United Kingdom Data Protection Act 1998 ("the 1998 Act")) for the following purposes:

We collect personal information from you when you communicate with us by any media. We may also collect personal data which relate to you from third parties

 **Sensitive Personal Information**

Certain personal information is categorised by the 1998 Act as "Sensitive Personal Data" as defined by the 1998 Act.

In some circumstances, Research Now provides you with the opportunity to inform us of your sensitive personal data, unless we are permitted to process such sensitive personal data under the provisions of the 1998 Act, we will ask for your consent. In general, the sensitive personal data collected by Research Now is limited to information in connection with:

In some circumstances we may ask about offences you have committed or are alleged to have committed and any proceedings taken in respect of such an offence.

 **Anonymisation**

Research Now conducts surveys on a variety of topics. Clients will give Research Now a brief setting out the types of individuals from whom we should seek answers. The brief will include matters such as age, ethnic background, qualifications and occupation. Research Now will review its database and then send out invitations to an online survey to people falling within the client brief.

Research Now provides clients with data files containing anonymous answers to survey questions or a report setting out and interpreting those answers. No personal data in respect of those individuals responding to a survey will be given to clients of Research Now.

Research Now will, from time to time, assist research organisations in other jurisdictions to survey people in the countries in which it operates. In these circumstances it will either send you a survey to complete, the answers of which will be summarised, anonymised and sent to the client or they will prepare questions for you to answer directly. In such circumstances your personal data are not transferred to third parties.  
 **  
Permitted Processing**

Research Now ensures that it is permitted to process your personal data. If no statutory condition applies to the form of processing we undertake, we can only undertake such processing with your consent. You may withdraw your consent to our processing your personal data for some of the above purposes by writing to the address below.

If a statutory condition applies allowing Research Now to process your personal data and you withdraw consent to process your personal data this will not necessarily mean that Research Now ceases to process your personal data as it may, for example, be under a statutory duty to continue to process your personal data for some purposes e.g. to keep copies of commercial transactions for a minimum of seven years.

Any personal information you send to us will be treated in the strictest confidence.

Research Now may continue to process your personal data after you have ceased to be a member of a research panel operated by Research Now, or a subsidiary or group company or if we have sent you any information you have requested.  
 **  
Sharing Your Information**

In some circumstances Research Now may be required by law to share sensitive personal data about you to a third party. Otherwise Research Now does not share sensitive personal data outside of the companies forming the Research Now Group without your consent. Your personal data may be shared as set out in the above purposes. If you do not wish us to share your personal data with any third party for marketing purposes, please write to us at the address below.

 **European Economic Area ('EEA')**

Please note that information displayed on our Website or sent to Research Now over the Internet may be transferred outside of the EEA, where data protection laws are not as strong as within the EEA. If you have any concerns in relation to such transfers, you should not use the Internet as a means of communication with Research Now.

 **Law**

Research Now processes your personal data in accordance with the 1998 Act. All processing of your personal data by Research Now is carried out in accordance with the 1998 Act. Research Now is regulated by the Information Commissioner for England and Wales. Following collection, save for any permitted transfers of those data to other jurisdictions permitted by the 1998 Act, all personal data collected from you are processed in the UK.  
 **  
Monitoring of telephone calls and e-mails**

Your telephone calls and e-mails to us may be recorded and monitored for quality control purposes. We may also intercept communications made to individual members of staff at Research Now when this is required for business purposes.

 **Cookies**

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to the Site. This can include using a "cookie", pieces of information that are transferred to an individual user's hard drive for record keeping purposes.

At the present time the cookie we send to your computer stores only basic information which you enter into the Site, which may include your name, address, phone number and email address. It is possible for Research Now to retrieve the information stored in the cookie, however this retrieval is unlikely at the current time.

Only information collected by cookies as specified in this section of our privacy policy is automatically collected from users of the Site. In the event that we do collect any personal data about visitors to the Site it is available only to Research Now.

The cookies function by saving your passwords and webpage preferences (including those preferences for the Website). As a result it is possible to speed up your future activities at the Site and allow Research Now to provide you with information specifically tailored to your interests. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. To modify your browser settings click on the help section of your Internet browser and follow the instructions.

 **Other Websites**

The Site contains links to other websites. Research Now is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices or the content of any websites which are linked to the Site.

Research Now encourages parents and guardians to use the parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help supervise their childrens' online activities. Research Now shall only obtain the data of individuals if it is permitted by the laws of the United Kingdom and shall take steps to ensure that children from jurisdictions other than the United Kingdom cannot use the Site.

Please check this page periodically for changes as Research Now reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of the Privacy Policy and the Site at any time. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this Policy will mean that you accept such changes. 

**Consent to Privacy Policy**

By providing the information requested by the Website, or by continuing to use the Website after having an opportunity to review the Privacy Policy, you have consented to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and Research Now’s use of the information it collects as described at the point of collection or in this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Website. **  
**

 **Contact us**

If you have any queries relating to this Statement, please feel free to contact us by letter at the following address:

      The Panel Manager  
      Research Now Ltd  
      160 Queen Victoria Street  
      London EC4V 4BF  
      United Kingdom 

**Definitions**

Please find below definitions of some of the terms used in the above privacy policy for your information and assistance. Please note that for the purposes of these definitions a reference to a particular gender is a reference to all genders.ProcessingIn the Act "processing" means obtaining, recording, or holding the information or data or carrying out any operation or set of operations on the information or data, including:
